# ANDREAN

# IT SUPPORT

## CONTACT

- 0899 8023 703
- Villa tomang baru Blok AB no.3A, Kutabumi, Kab. Tangerang 15560

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **SMK Bonavita**

2017 - 2020 Technical computers and networking

#### **Buddhi Dharma University**

2020-2024 Informatics Engineering

#### SKILLS

- Computer Troubleshooting
- Computer Networking
- Microsoft Office
- Scores 237 points for EPT EnglishScore by UBD (July 2024)
- Adobe Photoshop
- Computer Hardware and Software

#### **PROFILE**

A Bachelor's Degree graduate in Informatics Engineering, specializing in network specialists, with approximately 1 year of experience in IT Support. Skilled in technical aspects such as troubleshooting, installation, and configuration of both hardware and software. Experienced in providing IT technical support to users.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

IT SUPPORT

# PT Shinseong Delta Tech Indonesia, Tangerang July 2022 - December 2022

- Provide technical support to users, including troubleshooting, installation, and configuration of hardware and software.
- Respond to user inquiries regarding computer and software usage.
- Assisted users in resolving issues with computers and software.
- Performed installation and configuration of hardware and software
- Troubleshoot technical issues.

#### INTERNSHIPS

WHL (WAREHOUSE LOCAL)

#### PT. Mitsuba Indonesia

Maret 2019 - Mei 2019

- Received goods from suppliers.
- Stored goods securely.
- Delivered goods to customers.

## PORTOFOLIO/PROJECT

# DESIGNING AND BUILDING A CCTV SECURITY MONITORING SYSTEM BASED ON IOT USING ARDUINO MICROCONTROLLER (Final Project, Buddhi Dharma University)

March 2024 - July 2024

This research discusses the design and development of a CCTV security monitoring system based on an Arduino microcontroller.

This system is developed using a PIR (Passive Infrared) sensor that can detect movement in front of the CCTV. When movement is detected, the CCTV captures and photographs the movement and sends a photo and warning text message through a Telegram bot to users and security staff.

The data captured by the CCTV will be stored in an SD card module as evidence.

**Tools & Technologies:** IoT, C (Language Programming), Arduino Board, Arduino IDE, ESP8266, PIR (Movement sensor), OV7670 (Camera Module), BOT Telegram, Telegram.

**Link:** https://doi.org/10.36040/jati.v8i6.11740

# My Personal Web Portfolio

Developed a personal website portfolio using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Tailwind CSS, with guidance from YouTube tutorials and online course as part of self-directed learning. The website showcases my profile, technical skills, and project documentation. Designed with a modern, responsive layout to ensure optimal viewing across devices.

Tools & Technologies: VSCode, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Tailwind CSS

Link: <a href="https://portfolio-andrean.netlify.app/">https://portfolio-andrean.netlify.app/</a>